Imagine how you learn in school.
One teacher gives the same
demonstration to everyone.
During the lesson, different students
may all look like they fully understand.
However, the actual performance can
only be tested beyond the lecture.
Let's pick student A, give a real exam
on the same task and watch the rollouts.
How can we improve
student A's performance?
Give more demonstrations?
Tell only yes or no.
Or give an overall reward score.
But a score without step info
might confuse the student.
The reward may work after
tuning between A and teacher.
But when using the same method
for B or C, it may not work.
In school, teachers do not set
rewards differently for everyone.
They set a standard trial evaluation.
Now consider the same idea in robotics.
Each VLA model is a different student to
learn from the teacher's demonstrations.
We should also evaluate its
performance through multiple trials.
Inspired by human education, we are
considering the same for robotic learning.
Learn from useful rollouts and
corrections and avoid bad behaviors
while preserving each model's
learning and behavior.